Welcome friends, in the training of such friends,
friends, today we will talk
about accident insurance, which we will do
through the phone, so friends, first of all you have to
install the software in your mobile phone,
after installing it on the phone, you have to register,
as if you register, you will
see this type of interface in front of you,
as you see on my screen, so
friends, we are talking
about accident insurance here,
which is done in a great way through PhonePe,
so friends, getting insurance
here is very simple,
insurance is very compulsory for our daily life through PhonePe, so
friends, I am talking
about accident insurance here, so here
you have to come down by doing any direct on the phone
and
click on answer, as if you click on all, then
all types of
insurance will be shown in front of you, so here I
talk about accident, so
friends, here you see
life and accident, here it is simple, you have to
click on accident, as if you
click on accident, then this
type of interface will be seen in front of you  Now friends,
whatever insurance you want to pay here,
you can pay by selecting that insurance here, so
friends, let's say
I want to do insurance of 20 lakhs here,
then its up amount fee here is
780 friends and friends, its
policy is valid for one year, so friends, after
clicking on 780, you simply have to
click on Get Policy, as if you had just
clicked on Get, you will see this type of interface in front of you,
friends, now you simply have to fill in your name,
email ID and date of birth, click on the check
box, click on Agree and
click on Pay, as soon as you click on Pay, you will see
this type of interface in front of you, so
friends, whatever
bank is linked to you here, after selecting the bank and
clicking on it, the UPI
option will appear in front of you, you simply have to select your UPI and
pay here, so
friends, in this way insurance is done through PhonePe,
if you
liked this information, then do
not forget to subscribe to the Click channel and like, comment and
share the
information about the video.
Thanks for watching